Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 2 and District 2 Locals, 1936-1994 UE.4.1.2
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- District 2, 1.
  - District 2 Incoming Correspondence, August 14, 1937-May 31, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Ratner to Massachusetts Personnel Department Regarding Staff Members, February 20, 1953; 23.
    - David Scribner to Smith Regarding National Labor Relations Board, August 25, 1947; 24.
    - UE to District 2 Regarding Local 211 Finances, February 24, 1955; 25.
    - UE to District 2 Regarding Local 201 Finances, May 31, 1955; 26.
    - Unsigned Letter to William Murphy, January 7, 1940-January 21, 1941; 27-28.
  - District 2 Outgoing Correspondence, August 14, 1937-August 12, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Robert Adams to James Carey Regarding Staff Members, December 13, 1937; 1.
    - J.C. Almedia Telegram to Carey Regarding Matthew Campbell, June 2, 1941; 2.
    - J.A. Banks Telegram to Julius Emspak, February 25, 1945; 3.
    - Daniel Barry Telegram to Charles Newell, August 14, 1937; 4.
    - Walter Barry to Russ Nixon Regarding Address Change, November 6, 1947; 5.
    - Barry to Nixon Regarding Political Action Committee, December 2, 1947; 6.
    - Barry to Nixon Regarding Supplies and PAC, December 2, 1947; 7.
    - Mary Elyn Boland to Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, May 16, 1945; 8.
    - Donald Bollen to UE Members Regarding Lynn General Electric, Anti-communism and IUE Inter-union Rivalry, August 12, 1951; 9.
    - Joseph Calazza to James Matles Regarding Staff Members, September 21-24, 1943; 10-11.
    - Olive Chance to Janet Barish Regarding Staff Finances, February 18-March 10, 1947; 12-13.
    - Chance to Barish Regarding Finances, July 30, 1947; 14.
    - Nancy Cirillo to Barish Regarding Finances, December 11, 1945; 15.
    - Harold Conroy to Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, August 29, 1945; 16.
    - Conroy to Ray Klausner, November-December 1945; 17-18.
    - Conroy Telegram to Klausner, February 21, 1946; 19.
    - Jack Davis to Matles Regarding Supplies, January 14, 1950; 20.
    - Davis to Joe Dermody Regarding Everett General Electric, January 25, 1950; 21.
    - Davis to Matles Regarding Address Change, February 1950; 22.
  - District 2 Outgoing Correspondence, July 7, 1937-June 2, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Ann DeLancy to Selma Kuslick Regarding Staff Finances, February 19, 1947; 1.
    - DeLancy to David Ratner Regarding Staff Finances, March 10, 1947; 2.
    - DeLancy to Ratner, May 15-June 2, 1947; 3-4.
    - Ray Dunn to Emspak Regarding Waltham Raytheon Organization, April 28, 1943; 5.
    - Dunn to James Matles Regarding Waltham Raytheon Organization, April 28, 1943; 6.
    - Dunn to District 2 Locals Regarding Smith-Connally Bill, May 15, 1943; 7.
    - Dunn to Matles Regarding District 2 Meetings, July 16, 1943; 8.
    - Harold Enright to Emspak Regarding Dues, Political Action and Education, August 11, 1942; 9.
    - Joe Fine to Emspak Regarding Officers and Supplies, July 7, 1937; 10.
    - Thomas Fitzpatrick to Matles Regarding Local 229 Sprague Meter, October 14, 1946; 11.
    - Helen Grady to Janet Barish Regarding Staff Finances, February 18, 1946; 12.
    - A.D. Graham to UE Regarding Credit, December 22, 1937; 13.
    - Henry Gisey to UE Regarding UE News and Factionalism, August 11, 1941; 14.
    - Sam Gruber to Emspak Regarding Staff Finances and Samford Electrolux, December 26, 1944; 15.
    - Gruber to Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, January 2, 1945; 16.
    - Arthur Haight to People's Press Regarding People's Press, November 21, 1937; 17.
  - District 2 Outgoing Correspondence, April 18, 1944-March 29, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Harriet Goldring to Julius Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, April 18, 1944; 1.
    - Goldring to Janet Barish Regarding Finances with Receipt, May 4, 1944; 2.
    - Goldring to Barish Regarding Staff Finances, June 15-22, 1944; 3-4.
    - Goldring to Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, October 16, 1944; 5-6.
    - Goldring to Emspak Regarding Political Action, October 28, 1944; 7.
    - Goldring to Barish Regarding Staff Finances, January 18, 1945; 8.
    - Goldring to David Ratner Regarding Staff Finances, February 28, 1947; 9.
    - Goldring to Barish Regarding Finances, July 16, 1947; 10.
    - Goldring to David Scribner Regarding National Labor Relations Board, August 27, 1947; 11.
    - Goldring to Ratner Regarding Staff Finances with Telephone Bills, October 13, 1947; 12.
    - Goldring to Ratner Regarding Finances, December 1, 1947; 13.
    - Goldring to Ratner Regarding Staff Finances, February 21, 1949; 14.
    - Goldring to Barish Regarding Staff Finances, July 22, 1949-December 15, 1950; 15-18.
    - Goldring to Ratner Regarding Finances, March 29, 1950; 19.
    - Goldring to Paula Regarding Finances and IUE Inter-union Rivalry with District 2 Per Capita Payments, March 29, 1950; 20.
  - District 2 Outgoing Correspondence, November 28, 1944-May 8, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Mary Harley to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, December 15, 1944-January 8, 1945; 1-7.
    - M. Harley to Emspak Regarding Fort Wayne Singer, January 11, 1945; 8.
    - M. Harley to Emspak Regarding Finances, January 31, 1945; 9-11.
    - M. Harley to Janet Barish Regarding Finances, February 5, 1945; 12.
    - M. Harley to Emspak Regarding UE News, February 8, 1945; 13.
    - M. Harley to Barish Regarding Finances, February 9, 1945; 14.
    - M. Harley to Barish Regarding Supplies, February 15, 1945; 15.
    - M. Harley to Emspak Regarding Publicity, February 22, 1945; 16.
    - M. Harley to Barish Regarding Finances, February 28, 1945; 17-18.
    - M. Harley to Emspak Regarding Supplies, February 28, 1945; 19.
    - M. Harley to Barish Regarding Finances, March 2, 1945; 20.
    - Hugh Harley to Emspak Regarding Staff Members with Statement of Availability, November 28, 1944; 21.
    - H. Harley to Emspak Regarding Bridgeport Finances, April 3, 1945; 22.
    - H. Harley to Emspak Regarding Staff Members, May 8, 1945; 23.
  - District 2 Outgoing Correspondence, June 2, 1937-March 17, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - John Harrold to James Matles Regarding Taft-Hartley and Atwood Morrell Collective Bargaining, April 24, 1946; 1.
    - Florence Herzog to Julius Emspak Regarding Staff Members, April 9, 1945; 2.
    - Jean Horie to Matles Regarding Women's Conference with October 24, 1942, Minutes of the Women in Electrical Industry Conference Arrangement Committee, October 28, 1942; 3.
    - Horie to Ray Klausner Regarding District 2 Women's Conference with Conference Call, December 7, 1942; 4.
    - Henry Jean to Emspak Regarding Staff Members and Factionalism, March 17, 1947; 5.
    - Gertrude Kuslick to UE Regarding Staff Finances, August 16, 1943; 6.
    - Kuslick to Matles Regarding Staff Finances, September 22, 1943; 7.
    - Kuslick to Albert Fitzgerald, November 29, 1943; 8.
    - Perlie Ketchum to Emspak Regarding Rhode Island Organization, June 2, 1937; 9.
    - Leonard Lewin to Emspak Regarding Local 288 Finances, February 15, 1943; 10.
    - Richard Linsley to Matles Regarding War Labor Board with Matles Letter to International Representatives, March 30, 1943; 11.
    - Linsley to Massachusetts and Rhode Island Staff Members Regarding Political Action, War Labor Board and Staff Meetings, April 10, 1943; 12.
    - Linsley to Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, July 11-14, 1944; 13-14.
    - Linsley to Emspak Regarding Finances, August 23, 1944; 15.
    - Linsley to Staff Members Regarding Organization, October 18, 1944; 16.
    - Linsley to Emspak Regarding Staff Members, October 24, 1944; 17.
    - Linsley to Emspak Regarding Factionalism and District 2 Officer Elections, October 30, 1944; 18.
    - Linsley to Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, November 20, 1944; 19.
    - Linsley to Emspak Regarding Finances, December 4, 1944; 20.
    - Linsley to Emspak Regarding Staff Members and Organization, December 26, 1944; 21.
    - Linsley to Fitzgerald Regarding Finances with District Per Capita List, May 17, 1945; 22.
  - District 2 Outgoing Correspondence, April 22, 1937-January 22, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Madeline Maguire to Janet Barish, January 18-22, 1951; 1-2.
    - Herman Maillet to UE with "Today, the 'Boom' - and Tomorrow...?" Pamphlet, March 26, 1941; 3.
    - Jim Marino to James Matles Regarding Boston Stewards Council, September 29, 1948; 4.
    - Allen Markoff to James Carey Regarding Finances, June 28, 1937; 5.
    - Georgia McKinley to Accounting Department Regarding Staff Finances, July 7, 1945; 6.
    - McKinley to Matles Regarding Supplies, December 12, 1945; 7.
    - Robert Mintz to Emspak Regarding Finances and Organization, March 14, 1942; 8.
    - Jane Mobilio to Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, November 3, 1942; 9.
    - Thomas Molloy to Emspak Regarding Horton and Son Strike and United Auto Workers Inter-union Rivalry, April 22, 1937; 10.
    - William Murdock to Barish Regarding Staff Finances, January 9-July 14, 1947; 11-12.
    - Murdock to Seymour Linfield Regarding Taft-Hartley, July 28, 1947; 13.
    - Murdock to William Cahn Regarding Radio Broadcasts, July 31, 1947; 14.
    - Murdock to Russ Nixon Regarding Political Action and Political Action Committee, October 30, 1947; 15.
    - Murdock to Nixon Regarding Political Action Committee with PAC Collections, November 3, 1947; 16.
    - Murdock to Nixon Regarding PAC, November 17, 1947; 17.
    - Murdock to Nixon Regarding Stewards Classes, February 7, 1948; 18.
    - Murdock to David Ratner Regarding Finances, August 4, 1948; 19.
    - Murdock to Ratner Regarding Staff Finances, February 10-14, 1949; 20-21.
  - District 2 Outgoing Correspondence, May 18, 1937-March 1, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - John Murphy to Julius Emspak Regarding Addresses, May 18, 1937; 1.
    - Murphy to Emspak Regarding Finances, January 23, 1939; 2.
    - Murphy to UE News Regarding District Council Meeting, July 26, 1941; 3.
    - Murphy to Emspak Regarding District 2 Officers, October 22, 1941; 4.
    - Murphy to Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, November 5, 1941; 5.
    - Murphy to James Matles Regarding Staff Members, July 16, 1942; 6.
    - Murphy to Emspak, October 26, 1942; 7.
    - Murphy to Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, November 22, 1942; 8.
    - Murphy to Emspak Regarding Address Change, November 25, 1942; 9.
    - Murphy to Emspak Regarding Monsanto and United Mine Workers of America Inter-union Rivalry, December 3, 1942; 10.
    - Murphy to Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, December 21, 1942; 11.
    - Murphy to Matles Regarding Address Change, April 23, 1943; 12.
    - Murphy to Emspak Regarding Finances and General Executive Board Minutes, July 17, 1943; 13.
    - Marilyn Murphy to Janet Barish Regarding Staff Finances with W-2 Forms, March 1, 1954; 14.
    - William Murphy to Emspak Regarding Labor Department, January 3, 1941; 15.
    - Frances Olrich to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Boston Stewards Council and No-strike Pledge with Resolution on No Strike Policy, March 15, 1945; 16.
    - Tom O'Molloy Telegram to Matles Regarding Boston Stewards Council, October 11, 1948; 17.
    - O'Molloy Telegram to Emspak Regarding Boston Stewards Council, August 29, 1948; 18.
  - District 2 Outgoing Correspondence, October 12, 1936-February 9, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Elinor Parnes to UE Regarding Staff Members, April 18, 1946; 1.
    - Parnes to Janet Barish Regarding Staff Finances, July 3, 1946; 2.
    - Parnes to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Lynn General Electric and Factionalism with Boston Traveler Clipping, February 10, 1947; 3.
    - Parnes to James Matles, February 13, 1947; 4.
    - Parnes to Barish Regarding Staff Finances, June 4, 1947; 5.
    - Parnes to Barish Regarding Local 294 Finances, September 27, 1947; 6.
    - Parnes to David Ratner Regarding Finances, October 2, 1947; 7.
    - Parnes to Barish Regarding Local 294 Finances, October 2, 1947; 8.
    - Parnes to Selma Kaslick, October 11, 1947; 9.
    - Parnes to Barish Regarding Finances, October 20, 1947; 10.
    - Parnes to Ratner Regarding Finances, December 3, 1947; 11.
    - Parnes to Kaslick, April 14, 1948; 12.
    - Parnes to Ratner, September 15, 1948; 13.
    - Parnes to Ratner with Parnes Note to Ratner and Two Checks, December 24, 1948; 14.
    - Parnes to Kaslick Regarding Publicity, May 9, 1949; 15.
    - Parnes to Ratner Regarding Finances, May 24, 1949; 16.
    - Harold Peters to Fitzgerald Regarding Whitney Blake Organization and Staff Members, April 28, 1944; 17.
    - Leisle Rathborn to UE Regarding Greenwich Electrolux, October 12-28, 1936; 18-19.
    - Corinne Raymond to Ratner Regarding Staff Finances, February 9, 1950; 20.
    - Frank Reel to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances and William Winnick Case, February 11, 1938; 21.
  - District 2 Outgoing Correspondence, June 10, 1942-March 27, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - Charles Rivers to Julius Emspak Regarding District 2 Victory Conference, June 10, 1942; 1.
    - Rivers to Emspak Regarding Staff Finances with May 12, 1944, Receipt, June 20, 1944; 2.
    - Rivers to Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, September 6, 1944; 3.
    - Rivers to Emspak Regarding Leave of Absence, March 27, 1945; 4.
    - Bernice Rogers to Janet Barish Regarding Staff Finances, January 24, 1944; 5.
    - Rogers to Barish Regarding Finances, January 31, 1944; 6.
    - Rogers to Barish Regarding Staff Finances, February 1-3, 1944; 7-8.
    - Rogers Telegram to Barish Regarding Staff Finances, February 16, 1944; 9.
    - Rogers to Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, February 29, 1944; 10.
    - Rogers to Barish Regarding Staff Finances, March 3-April 28, 1944; 11-15.
    - Rogers to Barish Regarding Finances, June 2-July 13, 1944; 16-19.
    - Rogers to Barish Regarding Finances with Telephone Bills, July 14, 1944; 20.
    - Rogers to Barish Regarding Finances, August 1-23, 1944; 21-25.
  - District 2 Outgoing Correspondence, November 30, 1943-October 21, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Bernice Rogers to Janet Barish Regarding Finances, August 29-30, 1944; 1-2.
    - Rogers to Barish Regarding District 2 Officers, September 8, 1944; 3.
    - Rogers to Barish Regarding Staff Finances, September 28, 1944-January 16, 1945; 4-5.
    - Rogers to Julius Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, February 5, 1945; 6.
    - Vincent Romeo to James Matles Regarding Connecticut Malleable Castings Strike, June 7, 1946; 7.
    - Allan Rosenberg to David Scribner Regarding Workmen's Compensation with District 2 Disfigurement Survey and Results, October 21, 1953; 8.
    - Jack Simon to Emspak Regarding War Labor Board with August 1-November 13 Report on Agreement Cases, November 30, 1943; 9.
    - Simon to Matles Regarding International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers and International Association of Machinists Inter-union Rivalry, October 25, 1945; 10.
    - Simon to Matles Regarding Staff Members, November 7, 1945; 11.
    - Simon to Matles Regarding Wakefield Boston Sylvania Organization, November 7, 1945; 12.
    - Simon to Matles Regarding Staff Members and Boston Sylvania, March 13, 1946; 13.
  - District 2 Outgoing Correspondence, June 27, 1942-June 2, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - Albert Smith to James Matles Regarding Staff Members with Staff Assignments and Blank Report Sheet, July 21, 1947; 1.
    - Smith to David Scribner Regarding National Labor Relations Board, Taft-Hartley and Staff Members with July 25, 1947, Donald Tormey Letter to NLRB Regarding Taft-Hartley and Withdrawl, August 25, 1947; 2.
    - Smith to Russ Nixon Regarding Political Action Committee with September 16, 1947, PAC Report, September 17, 1947; 3.
    - Smith to Nixon, October 15, 1947; 4.
    - Smith to Matles Regarding Staff Members, November 12, 1947; 5.
    - Smith to Selma Regarding Address Changes, May 7, 1948; 6.
    - Smith to James Matles Regarding Staff Members, July 30, 1952; 7.
    - Smith to Emma Regarding Staff Members, July 1952; 8.
    - Geoffrey Spurr to Julius Emspak Regarding UE News, June 27, 1942; 9.
    - Jerry Steinberg to Matles Regarding Supplies, January 25, 1952; 10.
    - Steinberg to Ray Klausner Regarding Local 216 Constitution, June 11, 1952; 11.
    - Steinberg to Emspak Regarding Pittsfield General Electric, August 1952; 12.
    - Steinberg to Nat Spero Regarding Redwood, Rivett Lathe and Grinder, June 2, 1953; 13.
  - District 2 Outgoing Correspondence, December 17, 1941-June 5, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - Nick Tomassetti to Julius Emspak Regarding District Council, December 17, 1941; 1.
    - Tomassetti to Emspak Regarding District 2 Victory Convention with May 9, 1942, District Council Minutes, Credential Form, UE Victory Convention Leaflet and UE Victory Convention Program, May 22, 1942; 2.
    - Tomassetti to James Matles Regarding District 2 Victory Convention, May 22, 1942; 3.
    - Tomassetti to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding District 2 Victory Convention with Credential Form and UE Victory Convention Leaflet, May 22, 1942; 4.
    - Tomassetti to Tom Wright Regarding District 2 Victory Convention with UE Victory Convention Program, June 4, 1942; 5.
    - Tomassetti to Matles Regarding District 2 Victory Convention Program, June 5, 1942; 6.
    - Tomassetti to Fitzgerald Regarding District 2 Victory Convention Program, June 5, 1942; 7.
    - Tomassetti to Matles Regarding Staff Members, June 30, 1942; 8.
    - Tomassetti to Emspak Regarding Supplies, September 25, 1942; 9.
    - Tomassetti to Emspak Regarding District 2 Women's Conference Officers, October 19, 1942; 10.
    - Donald Tormey to Matles Regarding Staff Members, June 5, 1946; 11.
    - Tormey to All District 2 Staff Members, January 5, 1953; 12.
  - District 2 Outgoing Correspondence, May 20, 1937-August 9, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - Doris Venturella to Janet Barish Regarding Staff Finances, October 12, 1943-February 15, 1944; 1-2.
    - Venturella to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, March 14, 1944; 3.
    - Venturella to Barish Regarding Finances, July 14, 1944-November 12, 1945; 4-5.
    - Allan Webb to James Matles Regarding New Haven and Political Action, May 6, 1943; 6.
    - Lillian Weissman to Matles Regarding Staff Finances, January 3, 1941; 7.
    - Weissman to Matles Regarding Finances, May 5, 1942; 8.
    - Weissman to Matles Regarding Supplies, 1942; 9.
    - Weissman to Barish Regarding Staff Finances, July 24, 1943; 10.
    - Weissman to Barish Regarding Finances, August 17, 1943; 11.
    - Weissman to Emspak Regarding Staff Members, September 9, 1943; 12.
    - Arthur Wheeler to UE Regarding Bridgeport Brass, April 4, 1946; 13.
    - Michael Widman to James Carey Regarding Congress of Industrial Organizations, August 9, 1947; 14.
    - L.A. Willard to People's Press Regarding People's Press, May 20, 1937; 15.
    - George Wilson to Emspak Regarding Finances, November 7, 1937; 16.
    - Wilson to Matles Regarding Supplies, November 15, 1937; 17.
    - Wilson to Matles Regarding United Shoe Machinery, March 13, 1941; 18.
    - Frank Winn to UE Regarding Chapman Valve and Organization, February 21, 1942; 19.
    - Sylvia Zegar to Matles Regarding Staff Members and Hartford Organization, January 30, 1947; 20.
    - Zegar to Matles Regarding Staff Finances, April 8, 1947; 21.
    - Unsigned Letter to UE Regarding Hartford Organization, January 24, 1941; 22.
    - Unsigned Letter to UE Offices Regarding Factionalism and Anti-communism, November 27, 1942; 23.
  - District 2 Correspondence, March 11-November 1, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - District 2 Correspondence with Local Constitution and By-laws Booklet, October 28, 1942-December 29, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - District 2 Correspondence, July 8, 1943-April 1, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - District 2 Correspondence, January 9-December 26, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - District 2 Correspondence, January 6-December 3, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - District 2 Correspondence, January 29, 1948-December 14, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - District 2 Correspondence, October 29, 1956-January 1, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - District 2 Correspondence, April 24, 1959-May 26, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - District 2 Correspondence, August 24, 1966-December 10, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - District 2 Correspondence, January 20, 1971-May 31, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - District 2 Boston Correspondence, October 11, 1979-October 27, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - District 2 Correspondence Regarding Sylvania Agreement, August 24, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - District 2 Correspondence, January 4, 1984-March 20, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - District 2 Correspondence, April 9, 1991-December 1, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - District 2 Correspondence, 1941-1945 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - District 2 Salary and Expense Letters, February 27-December 28, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Albert Lamseit, February 27, 1943; 1.
    - Marian Danforth, February 27, 1943; 2.
    - Gertrude Kaslick, March 12-April 29, 1943; 3-6.
    - Danforth, April 29, 1943; 7.
    - Lilliam Weissman, May 29, 1943; 8.
    - Kaslick, May 29, 1943; 9.
    - Danforth, June 11, 1943; 10.
    - Weissman, June 30, 1943; 11.
    - Kaslick, June 30-July 14, 1943; 12-13.
    - Weissman, July 29, 1943; 14.
    - Kaslick, July 29-August 13, 1943; 15-16.
    - Weissman, August 31, 1943; 17.
    - Kaslick, August 31-October 14, 1943; 18-20.
    - Doris Venturella, October 29, 1943; 21.
    - Jane D.Mobilio, October 29-November 13, 1943; 22-23.
    - Kaslick, November 13, 1943; 24.
    - Mobilio, November 30, 1943; 25.
  - District 2 Salary and Expense Letters, November 30, 1943-August 30,1944 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Doris Venturella, November 30, 1943; 1.
    - Jane D. Mobilio, December 14, 1943; 2.
    - Venturella, December 28, 1943; 3.
    - Bernice Rogers, December 29, 1943-February 14, 1944; 4-8.
    - Venturella, February 28, 1944; 9.
    - Rogers, February 28, 1944; 10.
    - Venturella, March 29, 1944; 11.
    - Rogers, March 30-April 27, 1944; 12-14.
    - Harriet Goldring, April 28, 1944; 15.
    - Rogers, May 11, 1944; 16.
    - Goldring, May 12-29, 1944; 17-18.
    - Rogers, May 29-June 14, 1944; 19-20.
    - Goldring, June 14, 1944; 21.
    - Rogers, June 29, 1944; 22.
    - Goldring, June 29-August 30, 1944; 23-24.
    - Rogers, August 30, 1944; 25.
  - District 2 Salary and Expense Letters, September 14, 1944-June 28, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Harriet Goldring, September 14-November 21, 1944; 1-6.
    - Marh Harley, December 14, 1944-March 13, 1945; 7-14.
    - Helen Grady, March 29-April 27, 1945; 15-17.
    - Sylvia Fitzpatrick, April 27-May 16, 1945; 18-19.
    - Mary Ellen Boland, May 28, 1945; 20.
    - Grady, May 28-June 14, 1945; 21-23.
    - Boland, June 14, 1945; 24.
    - Grady, June 28, 1945; 25.
  - District 2 Organizers Vouchers, August 12, 1944-November 23, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Carmine Romano, August 12, 1944; 1.
    - Harold Conroy, December 9, 1944; 2.
    - Anthony Frasca, August 7, 1945; 3.
    - Anthony Songa, November 23, 1945-December 7, 1946; 4-6.
    - Sylvia Zegar, December 21, 1946; 7.
    - Songa, December 21, 1946-January 4, 1947; 8-10.
    - Edmund Rice, January 11, 1947; 11.
    - Songa, January 18, 1947; 12.
    - Joseph Chast, January 25, 1947; 13.
    - Songa, January 25-February 8, 1947; 14-16.
    - Anne DeLanch, March 1947; 17.
    - Darius Kline, April 1949; 18.
    - R. Donely, December 7, 1953; 19.
    - Joseph Zalis, November 23, 1955; 20.
  - District 2 Organizers Financial Reports, January 20, 1945-February 15, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - William Teto, January 20, 1945; 1.
    - Anthony Songa, December 7, 1946; 2.
    - Virginia Van Mayer, December 28, 1946; 3.
    - Songa, December 28, 1946-February 15, 1947; 4-8.
  - District 2 Finances, January 1, 1939-July 26, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Charter Supply List, January 1, 1939; 1.
    - Receipt, January 26, 1939; 2.
    - Paul Seymour Salary Check, June 14, 1943; 3.
    - Telephone Bill, July 12, 1944; 4.